{
    "id": "aa1ca8d9ab3548e78a06404c49409d74",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I waited for him …………………… 10 o’clock and then I went home.",
            "description": "Until and till are interchangeable. Until is more common in a formal style.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked for him everywhere …………………….. I couldn’t find him anywhere.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "hence",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will buy …………………….. you lower the price.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I did not enjoy the program, I sat through it.",
            "description": "Though and although mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. comes to the door, tell them I am out.",
            "description": "Whoever is used to mean ‘it doesn’t matter who….’",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whoever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you say, I will not believe you.",
            "description": "Whatever is used to mean ‘it doesn’t matter what…’",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I go to Mumbai, I try to see my cousins.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… you want is fine with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You should be ready ………………………… the time I come back.",
            "description": "The correct expression is by the time.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must finish it ……………………….. you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you repair my camera if I leave it …………………… Monday?",
            "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that will continue up to a certain moment.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "by",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can finish the work ……………………… Monday.",
            "description": "By is used to say that an action will happen before a future moment.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}